<Document>
  # Anomalies
  [color=#801ef7]Anomalies[/color] are entities of unknown origin. They are not properly understood and have yet to be conducted research on.

  Anomalies can present themselves in different shapes and forms, such as being an item, a person, a static object or even an artificial intelligence.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AnomalyPyroclastic"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobHoloClownGuardian"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobCatShadow"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ToyAi"/>
  </Box>

  ## Spirit Foundation Classifications

  Anomalies receive several classifications depending on these types of conditions:

  - Sentience
  - Hostility level
  - Containment difficulty

  Additionally, anomalies are also designated a code number and one official designation name:

  SF-XYZ-001-A

  The code is split with dashes. Each string between the dashes have their own meanings.

  String number 1:
  - SF: Spirit Foundation
  This is a header to make it clear, that an anomaly is being mentioned.

  String number 2:
  - X: Sentience, designated 0 for non-sentient, 1 for sentient
  - Y: Hostility level, designated 0 for harmless, 1 for safe, 2 for neutral, 3 for hostile, 4 for extremily deadly
  - Z: Containment difficulty, designated 0 for no breach capability, 1 for regular observation required, 2 for regular observation and maintainence required, 3 for impossible to contain

  String number 3:
  This string is the unique identification number of the anomaly. This number is simply counted up incrementally for each new-found anomaly, that had been transferred to the foundation.

  String number 4:
  Designation for a spawned sub-anomaly of the original anomaly (this part of the code is only added to sub-anomalies). This string usually follows an alphabetical order, such as starting with A, B or C.

  ## Code examples

  - SF-112-001: Shadow Cat
  - SF-000-002: Pillbox Of Gambling
  - SF-121-003: Magical Girl
  - SF-142-004: Duelist

</Document>
